noizemag.com 2012-05-01

# Noize Mag - Privacy Policy

| 

At noiZemag.com sm ("NM"), we respect your right to privacy. We explicitly ask when we want information that personally identifies you. By personal information we mean individually identifiable information about an individual collected online, including, but not limited to, name, physical or email address, telephone number, etc., that is associated with individually identifiable information ("Personal Information"). For example, we may ask you for your name and email address if you wish to register as a user of this Web Site, send us feedback, be informed of new features, services or products, or participate in a contest or promotion.

We reserve the right to collect and disclose (to our affiliates and to non-affiliate third parties) user behavior and Personal Information to the extent permitted by applicable law, as more fully explained in the Terms of Use [click to link]. We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it enables us to collect information about your visits to our Web Site. We may use this information to enhance your Web Site experience and may share some information with our members, vendors, sponsors or others.

We reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law (including, without limitation, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), regulation, legal process or governmental request, or to edit, refuse to post or remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in our sole discretion.

We encourage you to use caution and common sense in giving out Personal Information when using Company Community Services [click to link] or otherwise. We have no control over third parties to whom you may give Personal Information through the use of our services. We do not control the privacy policies of external locations you may link to from this Web Site. You should refer to the privacy policies and terms of use of such locations.

A Special Note about Children’s Privacy and Our Compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

You must be eighteen (18) years of age to use our Web Sites in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not intend to collect any personal information from children under 13 years of age. Our services target an audience well over the age of 13 and some content may not be appropriate for minors. Parental supervision is recommended. We do not condition the use of our Web Site by a minor under the age of 13 on such minor’s disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary. If you are the parent or guardian of a minor under 13 and believe that he or she may have disclosed Personal Information to us, please contact us at Webmaster@noiZemag.com. Upon request, the parent or guardian of a minor under 13 may review and request the deletion of such minor’s Personal Information, as well as refuse to permit the further collection or use of such Personal Information.

## Opt-Out

We believe that our ability to share your personal information with our affiliates and certain third parties improves our ability to provide services to you. However, if you object to our sharing of your personal information and would like to exercise your rights under the Financial Services Modernization Act and the Fair Reporting Act to limit our use of certain information governed by the mandatory opt-out provisions of those acts (should we ever collect such information and even though we are not governed by those acts), please print, complete, sign and return the opt-out letter available at Opt-Out [click to link].

Contacting Us about Privacy Questions or Concerns

If you have questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Web Site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at [Webmaster@noiZemag.com](mailto:Webmaster@CircuitNoize.com). or send a letter to:

Noize Magazine, LLC  
11333 Moorpark St #386  
Studio City, California 91602  

## Privacy Policy Changes

If we make changes to any terms or conditions of this Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted in this document in order to keep you better informed. We may change, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we tell you otherwise.

Legal Terms of Use
